kcjs.jp 2017-05-06

# None

Thank you for visiting the website of Kyoto Consortium for Japanese Studies (KCJS). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your personal information, we have developed the following policy.

## When personal information is collected

KCJS may collect personally identifiable information as appropriate to make the KCJS website more relevant and rewarding for you to use. We collect your personal information legally and fairly. We will notify you of necessary information regarding collection, uses, or disclosure of your personal information in some way when we collect your personal information directly or indirectly.

## How personal information is used

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests about our programs, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other programs that we believe may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our programs, to fulfill a request by you, or to contact you about your prospective, current, or past enrollment with us. 

We may also share your personal information with agents and contractors that we entrust service(s) and programs offered in the KCJS website. They do not use the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for KCJS.

We may also use your information to update internal systems. This allows for seamless delivery of services and resources to you.

## How your information is protected

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. We secure information transmission, storage, and retrieval.

Agents and contractors of KCJS may use your personal information to the extent necessary to carry out the services they are performing for KCJS. We strive to prevent unauthorized disclosure of your information, for example, by concluding a non-disclosure agreement.

We make every effort to protect information you provide to us against unauthorized disclosure, loss, damage, falsification of your personal information and unauthorized access to it by taking proper measures for safety. We strive to improve the way to handle personal information accordingly.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard your personal information, there is always a risk that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy policy or that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all Internet use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.

Third-party websites and services linked from the contents of the KCJS website independently set rules regarding protection of personal information and collection of it. The KCJS website is not responsible for these terms and activities set independently from KCJS. We urge you to confirm the terms of other websites before you provide your personal information to them. 

## Release of information to third parties and measures for safety

Without your consent, KCJS does not sell, rent, give away, or loan any identifiable information regardless its members to any third party other than agents and contractors of KCJS.

Agents and contractors of KCJS who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy.

When you, as the user of the KCJS website, request the disclosure of your own personal information that we collect online, we will inform you of this information to the extent feasible within a reasonable period of time. Other than such cases, we may release personally identifiable information when the disclosure of personal information is requested under law with which this website should comply (when the disclosure regarding information provided by users is requested by legal authorities such as courts, prosecutors offices, and law enforcement agencies).
